Butter Master in Suginami is
Butter Master in Suginami is famous for its financier.
but they also have a pudding that sells 1,500 puddings a month at the peak of its sales.
Here it is!
When you try it, you'll see
Hmmm...
It's firm and slightly hard.
The secret is
By using only egg yolks, the pudding is not too hard and has a rich and thick texture.
Good night!
Actually, we don't use egg yolks when we make financiers.
So we baked it with the extra egg yolks in a luxurious way.
I made a retro-style pudding with lots of caramel!
The pudding is firm and satisfying.
You can feel the gentle sweetness of the eggs.
Today, I would like to introduce you to an excellent pudding from a popular restaurant.
The pudding is making me hungry!
Sunsmile is located in Roppongi.
a pudding specialty store that sells 10,000 puddings a year.
The reason for its popularity
The reason for its popularity is that the pudding is made with the finest ingredients.
The eggs they use are
from Kanagawa Prefecture with a rich flavor.
The milk is
Pasteurized milk from Iwate Prefecture with a strong sweet taste.
The sugar is
Pasteurized milk from Iwate Prefecture with a strong sweetness.
We use Genius Sugar, which has a mild sweetness. The most popular of all is our Salted Cheese Pudding.
We use cream cheese to give it a rich flavor, and then add salt to give it a salty taste.
How does it taste?
It is very soft and melts in your mouth. It is full of cheese with a salty accent.
Curriedo in Shimokitazawa, as the name suggests, is a popular curry store, but their limited time offer pudding is also very popular.
It's the first time I've had it and it's amazingly delicious!
This is the green pudding!
It is made with strong-flavored Italian pistachio paste!
The pudding is made with Hokkaido cream cheese!
Strong strawberries all over!
It's a very firm pudding! It's a firm, firm pudding!
Finished with a homemade cherry sauce and pistachio cream topping!
How does it taste?
Soft and smooth!
The rich pistachio and fresh cherry sauce is delicious!
The white pudding is one of the most popular items at Akinpu.
When you try it, you will be surprised
Mmmm...
The caramelized taste is amazing!
In fact, there is a caramel pudding hidden inside!
Ricotta cheese is combined with egg and other ingredients
and add a generous amount of rich caramel.
The ricotta cheese gives the pudding a rich yet refreshing taste.
The pudding is then covered with fluffy cream.
and top it with caramel chips and caramel.
caramel chips and caramel on top.
Finish with a sprinkle of rock salt.
The caramel flavor is very rich and the saltiness is a nice accent.
All of the puddings are excellent!
Thank you so much for watching this video!
Please like, comment and subscribe to our channel!
Thank you very much!
This is Seika Inoue with Fuji TV announcer Shinichi Karube.
Seika Inoue, Fuji TV announcer
Thank you very much.